Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Audio, 1977-1992
  - Subseries B: Primary Audio Works
    This subseries is composed of primary audio works including recorded journal material, radio interviews conducted with David Wojnarowicz concerning the NEA and Donald Wildmon controversies, and recordings of Wojnarowicz's public readings and performances.
    - -1988 Journal Wojnarowicz / Journal 1988 Nov. Dec.; audiocassette TDK D 90, cuid26869 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0218)
    - -Act-Up Demonstration etc., June 1989; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony HF 120, cuid26870 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0219)
    - -Affair journal 3/81; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D-60, 1981; cuid26871 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0220)
    - -AIDS Vaccines, Gary Null Show, WBAI-5/18/90, NYC; audiocassette (F-4-A) BASF Ferro Extra I 90, 1990; cuid26872 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0221)
    - -American Dreamtime: NYC, 1984, by Doug Bressler and David Wojnarowicz; audiocassette (F-4-D) Maxell XLII-S 60, 092.0222 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0222)
    - -American Dreamtime, David Wojnarowicz & Doug Bressler; 1/4" analog reel, 1984; cuid26873 (Case 092.0160)
    - -Breakdown Journal NYC- Jan.; audiocassette D-C 60, undated; cuid26874 (Box 16, Folder 092_0223)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 63 minutes
      Currently available.
    - -Cross country/ great dreams- 1989, Pt. 1; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony HF 60, 092.0224 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0224)
    - -Cross country/ great dreams- 1989, Pt. 2; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony HF 60, 092.0225 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0225)
    - -Cross country/ great dreams- 1989, Pt. 3; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony HF 60, cuid26875 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0226)
    - -David; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; 092.0227 (Box 16, Folder 092_0227)
    - -David, John conversation, 12/31/80; audiocassette (F-4B) Scotch Dynarange, 1980; cuid26876 (Box 16, Folder 092_0228)
    - -David Wojanrowicz queer song; audiocassette (F-4B) FUJI DR-I 90, undated; 092.0229 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0229)
    - -David tape I, David tape II; audiocassette TDK D 90., undated; cuid26877 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0230)
    - -David Wojnarowicz, Friday, on censorship; microcassette (F-4-A) Sony MC 60, undated; cuid26878 (Box 16, Folder 092_0231)
    - -David Wojnarowicz & Sylvere Lotringer, Pt. 1; audiocassette Sony EF 60, 1989; cuid26879 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0232)
    - -David Wojnarowicz & Sylvere Lotringer, Pt. 2; audiocassette Sony EF 60, 1989; 092.0233 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0233)
    - -David Wojnarowicz & Sylvere Lotringer, Pt. 3; audiocassette Sony EF 60, 1989; cuid26880 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0234)
    - -Desire journal #1 of 2 / Affair journal; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D-C 60, undated; 092.0235 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0235)
    - -Desire #2 of 2 (Last Version); audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26881 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0236)
    - -Doug David, Storefront, Do not tape over this side; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D-C 60, undated; cuid26882 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0237)
    - -Success // Ending loneliness; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony CHF 90, undated; cuid26883 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0238)
    - -Hujar interview, tape 1; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26884 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0239)
    - -Phil: Health Stuff // Interview: Mary Hayslip re: Montanna's death 4/9/90 / Phil, Richard last tape; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, 1990; cuid26885 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0240)
    - -Interview with Ruth Hirschman-7/23/90; audiocassette (F-4-A) KCRW 89.9, 1990; cuid26886 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0241)
    - -Side 1: Interview with Ruth Hirschman-7/23/90, Side 2: ARTS/LA Tongues of Flame-8/13/90; audiocassette (F-4-A) KCRW 89.9, 1990; cuid26887 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0242)
    - -Interview with Susan Wyett/Artists Space, NYC/60 min.; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; cuid26888 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0243)
    - -Jesse; audiocassette (F-4B) Memorex MRX I 30, undated; cuid26889 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0244)
    - -John/David conversation 12/31/80; audiocassette (F-4B) Scotch Dynarange 90, 1980; cuid26890 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0245)
    - -Journal; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony EF 60, undated; cuid26891 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0246)
    - -Journal #2, 1988-89; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, cuid26892 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0247)
    - -Junk journal April 27-28, 1982, NYC // Jim Fourat/Junk Tape; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D-C 60, cuid26893 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0248)
    - -KCRW Radio interview with Ruth Hirschman; audiocassette TDK AV-D 120, 1990; cuid26894 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0249)
    - -Loneliness #2; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony CHF 90, undated; cuid26895 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0250)
    - -Hunke/Louis; audiocassette Certron LN 60, cuid26896 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0251)
    - -Some Cats Swing // Louis Cartwright tape 3, Finish up this side / Louis Cartwright 3TK4; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK SD-C 60, undated; cuid26897 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0252)
    - -Louis Cartwright tape 5 / Heavy Truck Drivin Poetry - "And a Happy New Year","Bologna la Influenza (Opera)", "Interrogation"; audiocassette Capitol 60, cuid26898 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0253)
    - -Louis last tape I / II; audiocassette (F-4B) Certron LN 60, undated; cuid26899 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0254)
    - -Louis last tape, Sept. 77 / Another Night at Columbia Side 2; audiocassette TDK D-C 90, 1977; cuid26900 (Box 16, Folder 092_0255)
    - -Lung and Casandra Starke Interview // Lung, Cassandra, Parental Abuse Interview; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26901 (Box 16, Folder 092_0256)
    - -The Manhattan Transfer Body and Souls / Wojnarowicz Public Radio; audiocassette TDK D 90, undated; cuid26902 (Box 16, Folder 092_0257)
    - -Paris-New York communications; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D - C60, undated; cuid26903 (Box 16, Folder 092_0258)
    - -Phil Z/David W. (Connie) / Phil/David (1st tape); audiocassette (F-4B), undated; cuid26904 (Box 16, Folder 092_0259)
    - -Ben Neill/Dis-Solution 2 // Journal / White House Press Schedule; audiocassette TDK D 90, 1986; cuid26905 (Box 17, Folder 092_0260)
    - -Ming Ma Cantonese / Performance tape (Languages) // Performance tape / Languages; audiocassette (F-4-D) Sony HF 60, undated; cuid26906 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0261)
    - -Phil/David [2nd tape]; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK SA 60, undated; cuid26907 (Box 17, Folder 092_0262)
    - -D.W.NJ.G.T. June 89 / (1) If I Had $ (2) Cuz I (3) Last Nite I Took A Man Home (4) Vision Piece (5) Goddess of Life + Death // Kostabi / Phil died; audiocassette Panasonic C 60, 1989; cuid26908 (Box 17, Folder 092_0263)
    - -Zwickler Demo A. Space; microcassette (F-4-A) Realistic MC-60, undated; cuid26909 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0264)
    - -Project Inform, Pt. 1; audiocassette Sony HF 60, undated; cuid26910 (Box 17, Folder 092_0265)
    - -Project Inform, Pt. 2; audiocassette Sony HF 60, undated; cuid26911 (Box 17, Folder 092_0266)
    - -Project Inform, Pt. 3; audiocassette Sony HF 60, undated; cuid26912 (Box 17, Folder 092_0267)
    - -Reading - Club 57; audiocassette (F-4-D) Scotch Dynarange 60, undated; cuid26913 (Box 17, Folder 092_0268)
    - -Releasing Guilt; audiocassette (F-4-G) TDK D-C 90, undated; cuid26914 (Box 17, Folder 092_0269)
    - -Richard Kern on Montanna 1990 (tape 1) // Richard Kern April 9 1990 RE: Montanna; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, cuid26915 (Box 17, Folder 092_0270)
    - -Richard tape VII; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26916 (Box 17, Folder 092_0271)
    - -(May 16 1982) NYC Self Conversations, Peters Loft, (RE: Sex / J.P. / Confusions); audiocassette TDK D-C 60, cuid26917 (Box 17, Folder 092_0272)
    - -Short Essay on Photographs for Madoka, NYC 84 3-5 minutes; audiocassette TDK D 60, 1984; cuid26918 (Box 17, Folder 092_0273)
    - -Sophie on Montanna, Tape V; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26919 (Box 17, Folder 092_0274)
    - -Chosen to Stay + Fight; audiocassette (F-4-G) TDK D-C 60, undated; cuid26920 (Box 17, Folder 092_0275)
    - -Steve #; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26921 (Box 17, Folder 092_0276)
    - -(Tape Journal) Clown laugh, use w/Doug // Recording #2 Steve Doughton, Philip Zimmerman, David W., Doug B. / Insane Laughter; audiocassette (F-4B) Maxell UD-XL II 60, undated; cuid26922 (Box 17, Folder 092_0277)
    - -Tape Journal; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26923 (Box 17, Folder 092_0278)
    - -Tommy tape VI // Tommy -Montana [2] / Tommy (partial); audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26924 (Box 17, Folder 092_0279)
    - -Tommy Turner on Montanna 1990 / 1/2 used: Tommy/Richard phone call; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, cuid26925 (Box 17, Folder 092_0280)
    - -Tongues of Flame Opening, 7/26 - 27, 90 Normal, IL- NPR Interview / Opening + Interview Blinderman / Wojnarowicz, Ina Jaffee NPR; audiocassette (F-4-A) KCRW 89.9, 1990; cuid26926 (Box 17, Folder 092_0281)
    - -Traveling; audiocassette (F-4B) Capitol music tape 60 minutes, undated; cuid26927 (Box 17, Folder 092_0282)
    - -Jan 1990 Panel Discussion w Paul Marcus, WBAI; audiocassette (F-4-A) TDK SA 90, cuid26928 (Box 17, Folder 092_0283)
    - -WBAI Panel w Paul Marcus; audiocassette (F-4-A) TDK SA 90, undated; cuid26929 (Box 17, Folder 092_0284)
    - -WBAI Panel; audiocassette (F-4-A) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26930 (Box 17, Folder 092_0285)
    - -ITSOFOMO Copy; audiocassette 3M R120 DAT, undated; cuid26931 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0286)
    - -Jan Bruce Audio Poetry; audiocassette Maxell UR 90, undated; cuid26932 (Box 17, Folder 092_0287)
    - -ITSOFOMO rough mix; audiocassette TDK SA 60, undated; cuid26933 (Box 17, Folder 092_0288)
    - -ITSOFOMO Final Mix / Meat Bloody Memory War; audiocassette Maxell XL-II 100, 1991; cuid26934 (Box 17, Folder 092_0289)
  - Subseries C: Sound Materials
    This subseries contains a collection of ambient recordings and a sound effects library that David Wojnarowicz used for the production of audio works and soundtracks for his films.
    - -Broken piano/musak/jack hammer/Rev. Swaggart Mix; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; cuid26935 (Box 18, Folder 092_0290)
    - -Bum Crash, Ship Horn, [Speed], Clocks, Firing Range, Chose to Stay & Fight; audiocassette (F-4-C) Ampex 60, undated; cuid26936 (Box 18, Folder 092_0291)
    - -Car crash; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 1, undated; cuid26937 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0292)
      TDK Endless EC1 cassette tape. The format is designed to loop endlessly and requires specialized equipment to play back.
    - -Fashion chit-chat, Queer dinner / Ready on the Right - Roll Back for El Salvadore Song; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated; cuid26938 (Box 18, Folder 092_0293)
    - -Gunfire Brian's song, Brian's song / Bum crash, Traffic report, Louis session 2; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 90, undated; cuid26939 (Box 18, Folder 092_0294)
    - -Hunger, Siren Pulse Beat, Buzzer, Surf / Crickets, Birds, Pool, Road Movie, Alcholism, Hold-up Tape [+] 10 Second; audiocassette TDK D-C 60, undated; cuid26940 (Box 18, Folder 092_0295)
    - -Windshield Wipers, [Buvsisles], Hut; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated; cuid26941 (Box 18, Folder 092_0296)
    - -KIDS; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 120, undated; cuid26942 (Box 18, Folder 092_0297)
    - -Mexico soundtrack; audiocassette (F-2) Maxell XLII 90, undated; cuid26943 (Box 18, Folder 092_0361)
    - -PRISON SEX, Sex Movie Music/Prison: Drums; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26944 (Box 18, Folder 092_0298)
    - -Queer riot fragments; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26945 (Box 18, Folder 092_0299)
    - -Reagan; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 1, undated; cuid26946 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0300)
    - -Sounds: Reagan Shooting / Down & Out in Paris & London, [Asteroids] - Galaxian; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated; cuid26947 (Box 18, Folder 092_0301)
    - -Reagan/various stations; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 3, undated; cuid26948 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0302)
    - -Recorder/Harmonica; audiocassette Realistic Supertape HD-90., undated; cuid26949 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0303)
    - **Missing**-Recording session w/ Doug Bressler 4/18 (no year given); 1/4" audiotape (F-3), undated; cuid26950 (Box 18, Folder no number)
    - -Garbage Truck in 14 St. Meat Market / Sex Movies; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; cuid26951 (Box 18, Folder 092_0304)
    - -Soundtape II USA / Hostage, Sing a long Stuff, Jerry Falwell Stuff: How to Raise a Family for Fun etc., Flood News, etc. // Soundtape II USA; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated; cuid26952 (Box 18, Folder 092_0305)
    - -Soundtape USA #3 / Plane Taking off N. Mexico, Spanish Movie (Black Cat Appears), Bed Rock City (Dino Barking), Water, etc.; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated; cuid26953 (Box 18, Folder 092_0306)
    - -Sound Tape #4 Oregon / Rodeo Party Oregon, Rodeo Party Keith; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated; cuid26954 (Box 18, Folder 092_0307)
    - -Soundtape #6; audiocassette (F-4-C) Realistic Supertape Gold 60, undated; cuid26955 (Box 18, Folder 092_0308)
    - -Soundtape #8, Alligator Tour, Louisianna, Storm Static Commercials; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26956 (Box 18, Folder 092_0309)
    - -Sound Tape 1985 USA / Elvis's Home Memphis, Approx. 20 min., Frogs in Swamp outside Jackson Mississippi, Train? '', Steps, etc.; audiocassette Maxell XLI-S 60, undated; cuid26957 (Box 18, Folder 092_0310)
    - -Soundtape; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell XLII 90, undated; cuid26958 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0311)
    - -Sound Tape, Oregon, Cows?, 6/2/95 C4 / Fire News/Prison Riot (Oregon) TV, Watermelon Pesticide, Fires, Rain Against Windows; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; cuid26959 (Box 18, Folder 092_0312)
    - -South America Argentina - Car etc.; audiocassette Citacrom CHF 90, undated; cuid26960 (Box 18, Folder 092_0313)
    - - Storefront: -Dealers on Bowery Chrystie, Car Accident, 14 St., Union Square, Wash. Sq., etc., Chaco, Joe, Dealers on Rivington; audiocassette TDK D-C 60, undated; cuid26961 (Box 18, Folder 092_0314)
    - -Side A Only, 25 min. approx., Times Square, 42 st., Midnight, Sat. Nite, 10-15 Min., Bowery Traffic, 3rd St. // Wojnarowicz/Street; audiocassette Maxell XLII 90, undated; cuid26962 (Box 18, Folder 092_0315)
    - -Swaggart / Musak; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26963 (Box 18, Folder 092_0316)
    - -Tracking plane / school kids; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 6, undated; cuid26964 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0317)
    - -Voices Distortion, Chosen to stay + fight; audiocassette (F-4-C) Ampex 60, undated; cuid26965 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0318)
    - -Pt. Wind; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26966 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0319)
    - -Wolf / George Jones, Amos Milburn; audiocassette (F-4-C) Sony CHF 90, undated; cuid26967 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0320)
    - -Soundtape / NYC ambulance // Wojnarowicz: Soundtape; audiocassette (F-4-C) Sony HF 60, undated; cuid26968 (Box 18, Folder 092_0321)
    - -"Crazy man sex house" and answering machine messages, audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26969 (Box 18, Folder 092_0322)
  - Subseries D: Original Music/ Wojnarowicz & Others
    This subseries contains original music recordings by David Wojnarowicz and the group 3 Teens Kill 4 No Motive as well as original and commercial music recordings by other Downtown NYC artists.
    - -New Song - Eye ect. - Visitation, Wind Up Clock - Woman of the Moose - 3TK4-NM, 2/81 / Gacy Song; audiocassette Maxell LN C 60, 1981; cuid26970 (Box 19, Folder 092_0323)
    - -3TK4; audiocassette (F-4-E) TDK SA 90, undated; cuid26971 (Box 19, Folder 092_0324)
    - -3TK4 BLAK // 3TK4, Specials Reserve, Dishes, Fisherman, Too much too soon, Falling Out, Place to Hide / Bite like a kitty, Look Around, Machine Age, Divine Liar, La Diosa, Jackie Oh; audiocassette (F-4-E) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26972 (Box 19, Folder 092_0325)
    - -3 Teens Kill 4; audiocassette (F-4-D) TDK D 60, undated; cuid26973 (Box 19, Folder 092_0326)
    - 3 Teens Kill 4 No Motive 7" Vinyl Sound Disc, 1982; cuid28640 (Box 149, Folder 37)
    - -Blank - Siren Cycle, Atomic Zone - Gun Cycle, 3 Teens - Atomic Zo; audiocassette (F-4-D) TDK D-C 60, undated; cuid26974 (Box 19, Folder 092_0327)
    - -Ben Neill, Two Dances / Mainspring c. 1986; audiocassette Maxell UDS-II 46, cuid26975 (Box 19, Folder 092_0328)
    - -Ben Neill, Mainspring, c. 1988, The Living Room, Inc., New York, NY; audiocassette (type unknown), cuid26976 (Box 19, Folder 092_0329)
    - -Evan Lurie, Happy? Here? With You? In Spain?, solo piano 2/85 Seltzer; audiocassette (F-4-E) TDK D 90, 1985; cuid26977 (Box 19, Folder 092_0330)
    - -Evan Lurie, Pieces for Bandoneon; audiocassette (F-4-E) Maxell XLII-S 90, undated; cuid26978 (Box 19, Folder 092_0331)
    - -John Fekner, Dennis Lattman and Sasha Sumner c. 1986: 1) Final Concerto, 2) Oil Drum Mix; audiocassette Sony CHF 60, cuid26979 (Box 19, Folder 092_0332)
    - -Rough mix, Visitation, Tell Me Something Good; audiocassette (F-4-E) TDK D-C 60, undated; cuid26980 (Box 19, Folder 092_0333)
  - Subseries E: Phone Message Tapes
    This subseries consists of phone message tapes from David Wojnarowicz's answering machine. These tapes document major events in Wojnarowicz's life including the death of Peter Hujar, and other friends, as well as the NEA grant controversy and the lawsuit against Donald Wildmon and the American Family Association.
    This subseries is arranged in chronological order.
    - -1985- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 60, cuid26981 (Box 19, Folder 092_0334)
    - -1985- phone message/ telephone '85; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 60, cuid26982 (Box 19, Folder 092_0335)
    - -1987- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, cuid26983 (Box 19, Folder 092_0336)
    - -1989- phone messages; microcassette (F-4-F) Code-A-Phone MC 60, cuid26984 (Box 19, Folder 092_0337)
    - -4/31/90-5/1/90-"American Family bullshit etc."; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, 1990; cuid26985 (Box 19, Folder 092_0338)
    - -6/2/92- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Certron LN 60, 1992; cuid26986 (Box 19, Folder 092_0339)
    - -July 1992- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Panasonic C 60, cuid26987 (Box 19, Folder 092_0340)
    - -May/ June (no year)- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, undated; cuid26988 (Box 19, Folder 092_0341)
    - -no date- "Time period of Pete's death" - Phone machine, phone message; audiocassette (F-1) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26989 (Box 19, Folder 092_0342)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Certron LN 60, undated; cuid26990 (Box 19, Folder 092_0343)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 30, undated; cuid26991 (Box 19, Folder 092_0344)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 90, undated; cuid26992 (Box 19, Folder 092_0345)
    - -no date- phone message side A; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 90, undated; cuid26993 (Box 19, Folder 092_0346)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26994 (Box 19, Folder 092_0347)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony C 60, undated; cuid26995 (Box 19, Folder 092_0348)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 60, undated; cuid26996 (Box 19, Folder 092_0349)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26997 (Box 19, Folder 092_0350)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, undated; cuid26998 (Box 19, Folder 092_0351)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK SA 90, undated; cuid26999 (Box 19, Folder 092_0352)
    - -no date- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, undated; cuid27000 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0353)
    - -no date- NEA messages; phone message, microcassette (F-4-F) Realistic MC-60, undated; cuid27001 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0354)
    - -no date- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Realistic MC-60, undated; cuid27002 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0355)
    - -no date- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, undated; cuid27003 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0356)
    - -no date- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, undated; cuid27004 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0357)
    - -Unidentified Tape: audiocassette Sony EF 60, undated; cuid27005 (Box 19, Folder 092_0358)
    - -Unidentified Tape: audiocassette, Maxell C 60, cuid27006 (Box 19, Folder 092_0359)
    - -Unidentified Tape: audiocassette, Maxell UD XLI 60, cuid27007 (Box 19, Folder 092_0360)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, undated; cuid27008
  - Subseries F: Commercial Audiotapes
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; cuid27012 (Box 20, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; cuid27013 (Box 21, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; cuid27014 (Box 22, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; cuid27015 (Box 23, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; cuid27016 (Box 24, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; cuid27017 (Box 25, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; cuid27018 (Box 26, Folder no number)
  - Subseries G: Dubbed Audiotapes
    - Subseries F: Dubbed Audiotapes, undated; cuid27009 (Box 27, Folder no number)
    - Subseries F: Dubbed Audiotapes, undated; cuid27010 (Box 28, Folder no number)
  - Subseries H: Unidentified/blank tapes
    - Subseries G: Unidentified/blank tapes, undated; cuid27011 (Box 29, Box 092.0161)
- Series IX: Photography
  This series includes photographs taken by David Wojnarowicz, photographs taken by other artists, photographs of Wojnarowicz' artwork, and source photographs Wojnarowicz was inspired by or incorporated into larger works. The majority of the contact sheets and negatives correspond to each other, and comprehensive indexing exists between the two subseries. Negatives can be found for most of the Wojnarowicz prints in this series, but have not been indexed in this way. A large numbered run of slides of completed artwork is accompanied by a list of each artwork's date and media; these seem to be pieces represented by Gracie Mansion Gallery.
  The provenance of Subseries A: Contact Sheets and Subseries B: Negatives is complex, and needs to be understood in order to understand the two subseries. In 1994, Aperture acquired many negatives and contact sheets from Wojnarowicz in order to use some of them in the production of the book David Wojnarowicz: Brush Fires in the Social Landscape. Aperture received 58 manila envelopes containing negatives and contact sheets, which they numbered. Other contact sheets or negatives arrived in "box 108," "box 109," "paper bag 111" etc. This original housing forms the basis for Aperture's system of organization. They organized and rehoused all the negatives, leaving contact sheets in the original envelope or box housing. Aperture also created a list of what they received, transcribing Wojnarowicz' notes, and listing the numbers of contact sheets and negatives in each folder. An abridged version of this list appears in the Container listing. All other contact sheets and negatives arrived at Fales Library also in manila envelopes. About half of these were numbered in red pen with numbers ranging from 2 - 41. The remaining envelopes were not numbered, but, as do all the envelopes, contain Wojnarowicz's notes about the negatives inside. A list similar to that created by Aperture was generated for these envelopes, and much of it also appears in the Container listing.